And in other news,
there's been a drastic increase
in sightings of UMAs,
or Unidentified Mysterious Animals.
What sets this story apart
from all previous reported phenomena
In fact, many of the witnesses
are active members of the police force.
as first responders were killed.
The images you are seeing
are the unidentified creatures
who have been attacking police.
You can even see the victims on the ground
here near the creature's feet.
All we know right now
but eventually she asked him
the one question
that lingers on every viewer's mind.
[anchorwoman] Those words
would prove to be her last.
[static crackling]
but it seems very likely
that they will continue to spread,
and no effective method
for dealing with them has yet to be found.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
we can infer that they most likely
came from the Balsa Islands.
There sure are
a lot of weird nations in that area.
Both the NGL
and the Republic of East Gorteau
are nations that choose to be
completely isolationist.
They're a whole lot
like this place, in fact.
[Bonolenov] I suppose that would make it
easier for the Ants to invade.
[birds squawking]
Wow. It's been a while, huh?
[Phinks] Hasn't changed a bit.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Huh?
we're seeing over 300 dead.
Bombs have no effect,
so we can't fight back against them.
[man] A few days ago,
he was an ordinary human.
So the Ants did this?
He's dead as a doornail, if you ask me.
The Assembly's debate right now
is if they should be declared dead
based on whether or not there's a way
to restore them to their original forms.
Okay, let me get this straight.
They can't avenge them,
They always lose sight
of what's important,
so we're gonna do things our way.
If anyone interferes,
we'll take them down,
as simple as that.
[Phinks] Before the day's over,
we'll exterminate this so-called queen.
My mother's greatest flaw
was that she could only produce soldiers
by laying eggs,
an archaic
and highly inefficient practice.
Her only success…
was giving birth to me.
Stop. Kill me! Just kill me!
[growls]
[Shalnark] Let's try the front door.
[Phinks] Sounds good to me.
Nobody's here.
So are they inviting us all inside
or what?
I'll go this way, I suppose.
And I'll go this way.
You probably have abilities you don't want
to reveal to us either, right?
[Kalluto] Understood.
[all] Start!
They've all scattered.
Judging by their footsteps,
I can sense that
these particular intruders are special,
[Zazan] Are they strong?
[Pike] They are.
[Zazan] Then go and get them.
I can't. If I did, then no one would
be here to protect you, Your Majesty.
Be careful, Pike. I'm counting on you.
[gasps] I shall.
Be right back!
[Zazan] Well, now then…
[servant] Off to join the fray?
[Zazan] My mother's greatest misfortune
was that she never experienced
the joy of combat.
[Chimera Ant] You're no fun.
Just let me hold you,
[narrator] Bonolenov is descended
from the Gyudondond people,
a small tribe chased into obliteration
by industrialization of their land.
When Gyudondond males
reach the age of three,
needles are used
to puncture holes in their bodies.
By performing different movements,
They are known as the Bap,
"dancing warriors."
Prologue!
that you will never defeat me.
[Chimera Ant] Hold on.
[Bonolenov] Don't bother
recanting those words.
They are nothing more
than the ramblings of a beast.
They cannot affect me.
[Shalnark] In a one-on-one fight,
my opponent's strength doesn't matter.
If I can stab them with this, I'll win.
But can I pierce that?
[grunts]
Those are pretty sharp.
The probability
of succeeding unscathed is 20%.
What the…
Why didn't it work?
I could have sworn I put the antenna in.
[Chimera Ant] You must be a Manipulator.
That must be the main condition
for activating your power.
You let your guard down
when you thought it had worked.
[Shalnark] Wow. This thing's name is Pell?
-You're a Manipulator, too?
-Huh?
My ability didn't activate
even though the conditions were met.
I'm very impressed that you could tell.
It's first come, first served
for Manipulators here.
And now all that remains for me
is to take you directly to the Queen,
and my job will be complete.
[Shalnark grunting]
I'm gonna give you just one more attack
before I finish you off.
You know some pretty big words
for a stupid Ant.
Fine. I'll take you up on that offer.
I choose a punch.
[gasps]
That one makes 11. Almost there.
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen!
Wait! Please, no!
KARMIC LOOP
[Phinks] Every time I wind my arm,
my punch gets stronger.
Ripper Cyclotron!
Oh, wow. Guess half of that
would have been enough by the looks of it.
I never know
exactly how much power to use.
Now, then, which way to go?
Right or left?
I'll just flip a coin.
Okay, so what's going to happen to me now?
[Chimera Ant] You'll become a slave.
You'll work for the Queen
until the day you die.
Not much different
from your current life, really.
[laughs] There's some truth to that.
It seems the only real difference
would be in whom I'm working for.
But if my choices are
die or listen to you,
[gasps] He just stabbed himself!
[automated female voice] Autopilot on.
[Chimera Ant gasps]
That's so much aura!
Terminate target.
Hurry up, Pell! Take his leg!
Remove the antenna!
I bet I'll be too sore to move a muscle
for at least a couple of days.
That's why I hate using this mode.
[Blinky babbles]
Ooh! Pretty powerful
for a little girl, aren't you?
I wonder where she was hiding that vacuum.
[Shizuku] The thread's strong.
If I get caught,
I won't be able to escape.
[Feitan] Not a funny joke.
What? A joke?
[over transmission] Brats like you
deserve to be punished severely.
[Bonolenov] They are nothing more
than the ramblings of a beast.
[Phinks] Fine.
I'll take you up on that offer.
[Shalnark] You know what? When I fight,
I always carry two antennae with me.
I wonder how I intercept.
[Chimera Ant] What's this? A child?
All right, little girl. Come over here.
[sighs]
Sorry, but I'm in a hurry.
[laughs] Okay. What's that?
Surrounding me with more paper?
[gasps]
You like hiding things on you, little boy?
[Feitan] As do you.
[choking]
[whistling continues]
What's the matter?
Weren't you attacking me?
I just assumed that you wanted
to stop my performance.
[screams]
[laughs] You'll pay for this!
I'll get Pike
to tangle this guy up in his thread
so he can't make a sound.
Well, you certainly do escape quickly,
but not nearly as fast
as the speed of sound.
[rumbling]
[Bonolenov] Battle Cantabile…
Squashed to death. What a tragedy.
[narrator] The Phantom Troupe
fight valiantly
to protect Meteor City, their home,
from the Chimera Ants.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Killua] Nog, erus.
[Gon] Hey, what did we just say?
[Killua] Hint: it was backwards.